foreign
[Music]
and thank you uh
should I use my or I can be without my
name
is
[Music]
number one private Company Insurance
Company
insurance
[Music]
company
number one is position
and number two
in Colon
and number one expiration insurance
as a number one company
[Music]
is okay okay
overall industry 20
to 250
Channel industry was very small today is
the industry of insurance as far as it
has touched 250 pm we are some of the
close 20 billion
so you can imagine the market today
finally we have seen a lot of
rollercoaster
[Music]
and minuses
but every cloud has a female name is
[Music]
people
were not buying games you know this was
an avoidable thing for people today this
pandemic has created so much of
awareness on healthy the key of we go it
is a
and which has created a lot of otherness
on health so healthy complicated foreign
[Music]
to create an affordable product is in
case getting more more advanced
coverages everything and to get all
these coverages on health or motor or
assembly the one thing which fundament
has made all of us too
talk about cyber incidents alone in
India
every year we see a rise of from 1866
657 percent increase of special
maintenance and if I talk about identity
test cases that India alone who were out
of 10 customers are susceptible to
Identity and it actually increases
Senses at your own life
so what is the Cyber Insurance
essentially cover the first coverage
that you have seen is unauthorized
transaction so any original price
transaction happening from your bank
account or mobile wallet or credit card
is basically what it covers the second
one is cyber exhaustion so also you
would find that we get regular rupee SMS
is on our mobile phone so that if you
don't update your kyc details today your
account will get locked up
[Music]
actually encrypts all your data and then
for you to decrypt that data pack the
corporate pressure demands his foods and
summary that is what is called a cyber
extraction
foreign
why I'm talking about these figures is
predominantly because there is an
enormous opportunity that lives with
existence and insurance penetrations to
developers do understand that this
technology
so moving on to the corporate Insurance
the first one is having graduating
sooner so what is basically a liability
insurance
office so liability is hard
ly the financial loss aspect and the
other one needs to be supporting usually
practice
Health advantages which covers Global
Citizens right it has a worldwide
compression it was
um
[Music]
so that is also covered in Health
Advantage class
es that the comprehensive when they
existing health coverage
if it is a cashless super resistance
first one to homogenate Industry again
to talk about anything which has come
into this industry as a new thing it was
launched by itself and when we come we
come with a technology
Superior technology rather than I should
say keep pressing plus technology so
that customer and the channel Partners
will use it to the maximum and they'll
have a seamless experience not only in
buying seamless customer experience
satisfaction of
the policy buyer Plus
seamless games
so
[Music]
um
your
you know how many kilometers were used
how much you want to pay and how much is
pending all things you can check if the
pay as you use there how to use
how many kilometers
launched
[Music]
foreign
so with this telematics device what we
do is we monitors almost around 8 to 10
parameters through telematic device we
monitor the usage Behavior
is uh
[Music]
Indus 2 latest updates